(Amy:)Then we'll track its progress
through our social group
(Amy:)and interpret the results through
the competing academic prisms
(Amy:)of memetic theory,
algebraic gossip and epidemiology.
(Sheldon:)Look at you, getting me to
engage in the social sciences.
(Sheldon:)You're a vixen,
Amy Farrah Fowler.
(Penny:)Oh, hey, Amy. What's up?
(Amy:)Sheldon and I engaged
in sexual intercourse.
(Amy:)In other news, I'm thinking of starting
an herb garden. Mum's the word. Gotta go.
(Bernadette:)Oh, hey, Raj, what
are you doing here?
(Raj:)I just felt like drinking alone,
(Raj:)because I'm deep and dark.
(Bernadette:)Uh-huh.
(Bernadette:)So, uh, Howard's not here?
(Raj:)No. It's just one of those
times when it's just you and me.
(Raj:)Like when the three of us
went to the movies,
(Raj:)and you and I waited outside
the bathroom
(Raj:)while Howard threw up
Red Vines and Cherry Coke.
(Raj:)Do you remember that?